<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[A Glimmer of Whimsy]]></title>
  <link href="http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2015-06-04T09:51:40-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Erica Naughton]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[erica.naughton@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internship Interviews!]]></title>
    <link href="http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/blog/2015/05/28/awesome-first-post/"/>
    <updated>2015-05-28T20:05:39-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/blog/2015/05/28/awesome-first-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[This week I am interviewing for summer internships! I'm meeting with Wellbe, Zendesk and Bendyworks. All three are very different companies, and I'm so excited to find out more! I'll keep you posted!
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Group Project!]]></title>
    <link href="http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/blog/2015/05/05/group-project!/"/>
    <updated>2015-05-05T19:21:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/blog/2015/05/05/group-project!</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We started a new group project last night!! This such a great opportunity to apply all the skills we&rsquo;ve learned and really shine!</p>

<p>So much progress has already been made.  I really enjoyed organizing all of our thoughts on to a white board with words and pictures.  I have naturally taken on a sort of project management role.  I have so much fun creating a new flow through our social media platform, creating to-do lists on our trello board, and making a google drive for us to share.  These tools will make the communication very efficient so we can make the most of these last 3 weeks.</p>

<p>The five of us call ourselves EveFy (our initials), but I like to call us EveFly :) The joke is that when Eve came into existence, it was the beginning of something great - like us ;) Half joking, because our team is made up of two boys and three girls. This will be fun!!</p>

<p>I&rsquo;d love to talk all about our idea, but we wouldn&rsquo;t want anyone to steal it!  So let the suspense build, and in a few weeks we will share our app with you!</p>

<p>Next week we are having our very own job fair.  Companies that have committed to mentoring us and taking interns for the summer will be at the event. They will pitch themselves to us and then we will have a &ldquo;speed dating&rdquo; style of interviews.  From there, we will organize real interviews with those companies!</p>

<p>Graduation is approaching so fast!  We will be having it at Dream Bank (on the square), at 2pm on Friday, May 29th.  What a beautiful place to celebrate our achievement!</p>

<p>Not only am I excited for the internship, I am eager to jump into the design world.  Attending Madison+UX in July will be a great launching point for my passion in design.  So much to look forward to! What a long way we&rsquo;ve come, and it&rsquo;s only just begun.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrapping Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/blog/2015/04/22/wrapping-up/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-22T13:55:39-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://ericanaughton.github.io/blog/blog/2015/04/22/wrapping-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So, I&rsquo;ve reached a place in my school work where I&rsquo;m quite ahead.  I have completed all my assignments for Javascript so far, though more assignments will be written soon.  Now I&rsquo;m learning a bit of jQuery, which has been a nice change up.  I am also freshening up on my HTML and CSS skills so I can finish up my personal website.  It&rsquo;s been quite a few months since I&rsquo;ve touched it, and I&rsquo;m pretty rusty!  But I&rsquo;ve created a new mood board and wireframe, so at least I&rsquo;ve got a new idea I&rsquo;m working with.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m glad I have this time to get reacquainted with these languages - before I start interviewing for an internship at a local tech company!  We will be having a personalized &ldquo;job fair&rdquo; in a couple weeks, which will allow us to meet representatives from different companies for which we will get to interview.  I&rsquo;m super excited for this next chapter of working for a real consulting company.  This will be one step closer to doing what I truly aim for - graphic design!  I&rsquo;m so eager to create new things and learn how to do it well from professionals.</p>

<p>Although I&rsquo;m thrilled for this new experience, I&rsquo;m also realizing how incredibly short of time we have to prepare portfolios!  Better get back to work!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
